<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Art FAQ on What Make Art</title>
    <link>http://whatmakeart.com/art-faq/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Art FAQ on What Make Art</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://whatmakeart.com/art-faq/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Art School Critique No Nos</title>
      <link>http://whatmakeart.com/art-faq/art-school-critique-no-nos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://whatmakeart.com/art-faq/art-school-critique-no-nos/</guid>
      <description>Critique No, No’s * (Not allowed without an explanation, give a reason why you think what you do)
Analyze the good and the bad. Keep personal feelings out of the way. Look at the work, what do you see? What do you think about the content as it relates to the assignment objectives? Tell us why. (an evolving and changing student driven collection)
No, No’s  I like / don’t like it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Critique Art</title>
      <link>http://whatmakeart.com/art-faq/how-to-critique-art/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://whatmakeart.com/art-faq/how-to-critique-art/</guid>
      <description>Art Critique What is a Critique? Many forms of critique exist but for now we will discuss the formal group critique found in many art schools around the world. It is essential to your training as creative professionals and will take time to master.
&amp;ldquo;A critique happens when a group of people convenes in an art studio or critique room to discuss and evaluate works of art. Depending on the class level, the school&amp;rsquo;s resources, and the area of study, the group is comprised of a combination of students, one or several instructors, and sometimes other invited participants, usually thought of as experts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Make Inflatables</title>
      <link>http://whatmakeart.com/art-faq/how-to-make-inflatables/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://whatmakeart.com/art-faq/how-to-make-inflatables/</guid>
      <description>How to Make Inflatables There are a number of techniques and materials that you can use to make inflatables ranging from the relatively inexpensive to quite costly.
There are two main types of inflatables, cold air and sealed. Most inflatables that you see are cold air inflatables. Sealed are inflatables are inflatable boats, balloons, mattresses.
Cold Air Inflatables Cold air inflatables require constant airflow but for a smallish inflatable a very small and relatively quiet fan can be used.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
